PAVARUTH BURANAKITSIN

GitHub: github.com/P-Buranakitsin **Phone:** (+66) 91-883-1723

Email: pavaruth.buranakitsin@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/pavaruth-buranakitsin-a717a8188/

SUMMARY

I am an aerospace engineering graduate from Chulalongkorn University who enjoys solving programming problems. My passion for coding started when I was working on my senior project, which involved software development. Ever since then, I have aimed to work as a software engineer or software developer.

Although coming from an aerospace engineering background, I do have programming experience through courses, projects and my current profession as a front-end developer; the details about my senior project, certificates and some minor coding-related projects are available on my GitHub and LinkedIn links.

EDUCATION

B.E. Chulalongkorn University,

Aerospace Engineering (International Program)

2016 - 2020

GPAX: 3.04

COMPUTER SKILLS

Programming Language: Python, Golang, JavaScript, Java, Typescript

Software: MATLAB

Framework: React, React Native

Database: MySQL

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer | Cheddo Technology

JAN 2020 – PRESENT

- Develop features to enhance the user experience using React and React Native
- Optimize both website and mobile application for maximum speed
- Integrate APIs endpoints in frontend applications
- Ensure that the designs for both website and mobile application are responsive

Intern | Triumph Group

JUN 2019 – JUL 2019

- Performed adhesive bond strength tensile lap shear testing under supervision of experienced technicians
- Assisted design engineers in components scanning
- Assisted design engineers in technical drawings

Intern | Thai Airways International

JUN 2018 – JUL 2018

- Learnt how to use Aircraft Maintenance Manual (AMM) based on real-life cases
- Visited several workshops at Suvarnabhumi International Airport: Oxygen Distribution System, Aircraft Structure Reparation, and Brake & Wheel to review their responsibilities

PROJECTS

Senior Project | Development of MATLAB Application

JAN 2020 – MAY 2020

- Developed MATLAB application to solve two-dimensional diffusion equation by Bubnov-Galerkin method on triangular

Minor Project Expense Calculator - Designed and developed expense calculator website using	2020
vanilla JavaScript Minor Project Contact Android App - Designed and developed contact app on Android using React-Native	2020
framework	
Minor Project Math Quiz - Developed math quiz app using Golang	2020
 Minor Project Fatal Shootings in the US by Police Officers Explored, analyzed, and created models from "fatal shootings in the U by police officers" dataset using Python 	2020 JS
CERTIFICATIONS	
Certificate of Completion Achieve Challenge: Python For Data Science 35 Days - Issued by Bangkok Innovation House on Sep 9, 2020 Certificate of Completion Thinking Like A Programmer Pathway (Gold Award)	
- Issued by Chulalongkorn University on Aug 31, 2020	
Certificate of Completion Learn How To Code: Golang Programming Language - Issued by Udemy on Aug 28, 2020	
Certificate of Completion Business Intelligence Analyst Course - Issued by Udemy on Jun 2, 2020	
LANGUAGES	
Thai: Native Language	
English: Advanced Working Proficiency according to TOEIC (975 / 990)	
EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES & VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE	
CU AERO Annual Camp - Participated in camp activities	2016 – 2020
Paper Ranger - Created notebooks from used paper for children in need	FEB 2019

CU-KU AERO Volunteer Camp
- Participated in volunteer activities to conserve forests by planting

sampling

2017 - 2019